# **Ryan Thomson**

ryan@makegames.dev | (+44) 7964732277 | ryan.makegames.dev

### **Profile**

Full stack object-orientated programmer who specializes in games programming. Strong working knowledge of maths, algorithms, and data structures commonly found within games. Naturally able to quickly pickup and acclimate to new programming languages, tools, software, and development environments. Comfortable working within a team or independently.

### Skills

**Programming:** C++, C, C#, Java, Python, Node.js, SQL/NoSQL

**Production:** Jira, Confluence, Trello

**Software:** Visual Studio, VSCode, Rider, IntelliJ, Unreal Engine, Unity

## **Work Experience**

**Pocket Sized Hands Limited** 

**Games Programmer** 

01/2020 - Present

Create, develop, and maintain game applications for third party clients. Typically using Unreal Engine (C++) or Unity (C#). Experience with all stages of game development.

- Solely developed a VR game prototype for a client.
- Remastered a previously released Unity game using Unreal Engine.

#### **Tag Games**

**Games Programmer** 

03/2020 - 09/2020

Contracted through Pocket Sized Hands to work here for 6 months.

Contributed to the development and maintenance of a popular mobile game.

- Helped develop a major game feature relating to micro-transactions.
- Bug fixed through Jira and an external third-party QA team.

Education	Awards	
University of Abertay Dundee	09/2018	Tranzfuser
09/2015 - 05/2018	09/2017	Dare Academy
(BSc) Computer Games Technology	09/2016	A D D McKay Senior Prize